{"data":[{"question":"She ______ me that.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"3","explain":"- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something\n\n- Simple past tense: tell- told","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't _______ him anything yet.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't ______ her anything yet!","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Did they ______ you what to do?","a":"told","b":"say","c":"tell","d":"said","answer":"3","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What did your teacher _______ about it?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- What\/which + did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What did your nephew ______ last night?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- What\/which + did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher ______ him the answer.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"3","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Simple past tense: tell- told ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Johnny, always ______ the truth!","a":"tell","b":"said","c":"say","d":"told","answer":"1","explain":"- To tell (you) the truth: used to emphasize that you are being very honest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll ______ them when I see them.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"That is what he _______.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Simple past: say- said","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}